Phone: (318) 245-9708 Email: knf010@latech.edu

## **Kennedy North Ford**

### **Summary**

Enthusiastic and dedicated student with a desire to learn and grow through every work experience that they are able to ascertain. Willing to do any and every task that is required of them, and almost overly motivated to achieve the very best result possible. Everything that they will do will be done to the best of their abilities and with the greatest amount of excellence possible.

## **Programming Languages**

Adept/Intermediate level knowledge:

- Python, Java, C, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Introductory/Basic Knowledge:

- Bash, Assembly

## **Work History**

#### LaTech Computing Center Help Desk, Ruston, LA - IT associate

Sept. 2021 - Present

- Worked to help LaTech students & faculty troubleshoot their IT issues in person.
- Answered phone calls and assisted customers remotely.

#### MidSouth Pecan, Ruston, LA - Multipurpose worker

Sept. 2019 - Nov. 2020

- Cleaned, packaged, and stocked product
- Worked with shipping product to clients around the US
- Monitored heavy machinery

### Education

# **Louisiana Tech University | Ruston, LA** — Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Sept. 2019 - Current

Junior computer science major concentrating in Cyber Security as well as Cloud Computing and Big Data who, thus far, has taken classes pertaining to Data Structures, Advanced Data Structures, Operating Systems, Systems Programming, Cyber Security, etc.

## Union Christian Academy, Farmerville, LA - High School

Sept. 2017 - May 2019

Homeschooled through the 10th grade, and then decided to transfer to a private institution to complete a high school education as well as to complete 30+ hours of dual-enrollment credit. Finished school and graduated with a 3.9 GPA (on a 4.0 scale)